Previously on White Collar...
"妙警賊探"前情提要...
The Mosconi Codex.
莫斯克尼法典
This is no ordinary book.
不是一般的書
I think Hagen is using you.
我覺得Hagen在利用你
The only chance we have of getting a leg up on him
事先破解法典
is by deciphering the codex first.
是我們獲得優勢的唯一機會
- Neal took off,didn't he? - Yeah,he sure did.
- Neal溜了 是吧? - 必須的
Find out where he went.
查查他去了哪裡
Surveillance cameras a block from the vodka room led us to a cabbie.
伏特加酒屋一個街區之外的攝像頭 讓我們找到一輛計程車
Is there any reason he'd slip away to come here?
有什麼他需要溜到這裡的理由嗎?
Neal always has a reason.
Neal總是有理由的
You okay?
你沒事吧?
I can't exhale until I hear you walk through that door at night.
直到晚上聽見你進了門 我才能鬆一口氣
Agent Siegel's murder was a random act of violence.
Siegel探員的死是一場 意外的暴力事件
But it's not gonna happen to me.I promise.
但是這不會發生在我身上 我保證
But the codex has been hidden away its entire existence.
但是法典不知道被藏到哪裡了
How did you get a copy?
你們怎麼會有?
Our copy of the codex is incomplete.
我有的法典並不全
How much do you have?
你有多少?
A single chapter.
只有一章
It's chapter 13.
第13章
In all the books he ever produced,
他所有的書裡
he never wrote a chapter 13.
都沒有第13章
Haircut,new suit.
新髮型 新西裝
What's the occasion?
什麼情況?
On this very day,I walked into a downtown art gallery
就是在這一天 我走進市區一家藝術畫廊
and first laid eyes on my future wife.
邂逅了我未來的妻子
Ah,routine art crime investigation
例行的藝術罪案調查
turns into the luckiest day of your life.
卻成了你生命中最幸運的一天
I agree.
不錯
And to celebrate,we're going to the same restaurant
為了慶祝一下
- we went to on our first date. - Papaya King?
- 我們要去第一次約會的那間飯店吃飯 - Papaya King?
La Cucina de Tua Nonna.
La Nonna Cucina酒吧
Red sauce,wine in straw bottles.
紅色的醬汁 裝在吸管瓶中的紅酒
Napkin tucked into your collar?
以及塞在領子裡的餐巾?
I'm making it a point to remember all the anniversaries.
我要強調的是記住所有的紀念日
Birthdays,weddings,the day we brought Satchmo home from the breeders.
生日 結婚紀念日 把Satchmo從繁育者那領回家的日子
I imagined a stork delivery.
我以為是鸛送來的呢
- December 7th. - Pearl Harbor day?
- 12月7日 - 珍珠港事件紀念日?
Another day that will live in infamy.
另一個遺臭萬年的日子
First time I arrested you.
是我第一次抓到你的日子
- Hmm,and four years later we did it all over again. - Yeah.
- 並且四年之後又重新上演一次 - 是
But this time,you gave me jewelry.
你這次還送我一件首飾
Which is why I asked you to meet me here.
所以我叫你到這裡
I removed your anklet
我摘了你的腳環
for our undercover operation at the vodka room.
是為了在伏特加酒屋的臥底行動
Soon after,I found this.
之後 我發現這個
Don't we have hundreds of those back at the office?
辦公室裡不是一大把的?
I have a hunch this has special significance.
我有預感 這一枝有特殊的意義
Office building,56th Street.
56號大街的辦公樓
Gravich Chiropractic.
Gravich整骨醫師
Our next case.
我們的下一個案子
Could be mine.
可能是我的下一個案子
I'm here to help.
樂意效勞
You can go home now.
你現在可以回家了
This year,skip the straw bottle wine.
今年別點吸管瓶紅酒了
Spring for some sangiovese.
試試桑嬌維塞
I'll order what I always order.
我還是按我原來的點
I downloaded it to my phone so I'd always have it with me.
我下載到手機上 便於隨身攜帶
I still love Italian.
我現在還愛著意大利呢
I still love you.
而我還愛著你
So am I the first guy you ever made a sign for?
我是第一個讓你為之寫牌子的人?
It was the first sign that didn't say "Go away."
是第一個沒有讓我寫"滾開"的人
Oh,it wouldn't have discouraged me.
就算你寫了我也不會喪氣
Did you ever think where you would be
你有想過如果那天你沒有走進我的畫廊
if you didn't walk into my gallery that day?
現在會怎樣嗎?
Nope. Never.
沒有 從沒想過
Too scary to think about.
只有想像也夠嚇人了
How's work going? Getting any better?
工作怎麼樣? 有好消息嗎?
Yeah,we added Siegel's picture to the honor wall.
我們把Siegel的照片掛在榮譽牆上
That was something,at least.
至少是為他做了些什麼
Hey,what kind of celebration is this?
這算什麼慶祝啊
- Glasses are almost empty. - Thank you.
- 杯子都空了 - 謝謝
Scusi.
打擾一下
We didn't order these.
我們沒點這個
What's wrong? Do you know her?
怎麼了? 認識她?
I think I do.
好像是的
That's Jill.
是Jill
Jill.
Jill
From Quantico.
匡提科那個
Oh,that's Jill?
她就是Jill?
Right. My ex-girlfriend.
是 我的前女友
- Peter. - Yes.
- Peter - 你好
It's been a long time.
好久不見
20 years long.
20年了
I never thought I'd see you here,tonight.
沒想到今天會在這裡遇到你
I hunted you down.
我特意找的你
This is my wife,Elizabeth.
這位是我的妻子 Elizabeth
It's great to meet you.
很高興見到你
Uh,wait,I've interrupted something.
等等 我是不是打擾你們了
Oh,no.This is just an average Tuesday night for us,right?
沒有 不過是平常的晚餐 是吧?
Come on,sit down. Join us.
來吧 和我們一起坐
- Okay. - Okay.Okay.
- 好啊 - 好的
So,um,what are you doing in New York?
你來紐約做什麼?
I'm on a case. Thought I'd look you up.
查一件案子 於是想見你一面
How'd you find me?
你怎麼找到我的?
That's what I do,Peter.
我就是做這一行的 Peter
You still in SSG?
你還在SSG?
Last time I checked in.
一直在這裡
What's SSG?
SSG是什麼?
SSG: Special surveillance group.
特別監控組
We track down the bad guys,follow 'em,
追查罪犯的行蹤 跟蹤他們
record 'em if we can.
如果可以的話就監聽
Sounds fascinating.
聽起來很有趣
- You still drink bourbon? - On occasion.
- 現在還喝波旁嗎? - 偶爾
Well,this is a damn special one.How about you?
這可是特別的一種 你喝嗎?
Sure,why not?
喝啊 怎麼不喝?
Remember our toast?
還記得我們的祝酒詞?
Truth,justice...
真相 公正
And stay out of our way.
別擋著我的路
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=http://ytet.org=-   proudly presents
-=伊甸園美劇 http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=伊甸園字幕站 http://ytet.org=- 榮譽出品 本字幕僅供學習交流，嚴禁用於商業途徑
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-Sync: YTET- 爱吃鱼的老虎  静静的生活
-=YTET-伊甸園字幕組=- 翻譯: 郭郭 安 Zzinc Muslin 泉雋戈弘 校對: 時差雪 時間軸:愛吃魚的老虎  靜靜的生活
White CollarS05E07
妙警賊探 第五季 第 7 集
Here it is.
請進
Every time I pass this house I was tempted to knock and ask for a look inside.
每次路過這棟房子 總想敲門進來看一眼
Oh,you should have.
真該這麼做
My landlady would have invited you in for coffee.
我的房東甚至會請你喝杯咖啡
God,it's like a good book I'm finally getting to read.
天 就像是終於讀到了 我垂涎已久的那本書
I can't believe you live here.
無法相信你竟然住在這裡
Well,I just rent the epilogue.
我只是租了一小間
Can I get you a glass of wine?
來杯紅酒?
FBI agents are allowed to drink on the job?
FBI的探員允許在工作時間喝酒?
Well,we're always on the job.What choice do we have?
我們隨時待命 還有別的選擇嗎?
And now that you're joining us,I'm gonna corrupt you too.
現在你加入進來 也要被我帶壞了
Thank you.
謝謝
So where's this phantom chapter 13 of yours?
你那神秘的第13章在哪?
Right here.
這裡
- It can't be. - Why? What's wrong?
- 不可能 - 為什麼? 哪裡有問題?
What's wrong is that it's right.
有問題的就是這太完全沒問題
It's--it--it's a Mosconi,but that's impossible.
這... 這就是Mosconi寫的 但是不可能啊
That would make it the only chapter 13 that he ever made.
這是他所有作品中唯一出現的第13章
Well,it was copied directly from the codex at the Gershon Museum.
這是從Gershon博物館的 法典上直接複製的
It is his handwriting.
就是他的筆跡
This is crazy.
太不可思議了
And this.
還有這個
Here.
這裡
It's a study for a painting.
這是關於繪畫作品的研究
That he didn't put on canvas until a year after this was published.
法典出版一年之後 他才畫出來
So these pages,they couldn't have been done by anyone else.
這些內容 不可能由他人代筆
And this has to be from his New York period.
並且是他在紐約期間所做
1886.He was here less than a year.
1886年 他曾在這裡大半年的時間
FBI art crimes database.
FBI藝術犯罪科有數據庫
Maybe he wrote his only chapter 13 in New York as well.
也許這僅有的第13章 也是他在紐約完成的
Well,Mosconi rushed back to Italy in a hurry.
Mosconi匆忙趕回意大利
The why he ran is a mystery.
原因卻無人所知
And the book he left us is more of a what than a why.
而他留下的這本書也是內容多過原因
He was a puzzling man who loved puzzles.
他原本就是喜歡謎題的神秘男子
See,Mosconi believed that if someone wanted the truth,
Mosconi堅信如果想要瞭解真相
they should have to search for it.
必須用心搜尋
What--what are you doing?
你在幹嘛?
If this book is a puzzle,maybe these are the pieces.
如果這本書是個謎題 也許這些就是組成拼圖的碎片
Look at that.
看這個
Come here.
過來
Oh,my gosh.
我的天
Here's one.
還有這個
Where's the middle?
中間的在哪?
It's gotta be here somewhere.
肯定在什麼地方呢
- It's incredible. - It looks like a stained glass window.
- 不可思議 - 看起來很像染彩玻璃窗
But if he wrote chapter 13 when he was in New York,
如果他是在紐約寫下的第十三章
this stained glass window could be right here in Manhattan.
這塊玻璃窗應該就在這兒 在曼哈頓
Do you--do you realize what you've just done?
你 有沒有意識到自己剛做了什麼?
Made a mess of the codex?
把法典的搞亂了?
No,I-I think you might have just made
不 我想你很有可能做出了幾十年來
one of the most important discoveries on Mosconi in decades.
關於莫斯克尼研究裡的最重要的發現
Ah,working into the night?Impressive.
工作到深夜? 真出色
You should know the FBI frowns on overtime.
你得知道 FBI不鼓勵加班
- Uh,we--we've made incredible progress,sir.- Yes.
- 我們有了重大突破 先生 - 好
- I'm gonna let Agent Caffrey fill you in. - Sure.
- 我會讓Caffrey探員提供詳情 - 可以
You know,I'm gonna...research this window.
我想要... 研究一下那個窗戶
See if I can find out where it is.
看看我能不能找到它在哪兒
Yeah,I'll put my FBI resources on it as well.
好 我也會把FBI的資源集中於此事
- We can see who finds it first. - 'Kay.
- 我們看看誰先找到它 - 好
What?
怎麼了?
You,business,and women...the unholy trinity.
你 工作 還有女人... 簡直是邪惡的三位一體
Rebecca is all about the business of the codex.
Rebecca來只是為了法典的事
Oh,like I've never seen this before.
別說的好像我沒見過你同樣的境況
Kate,Alex,Sarah.Now Rebecca.
Kate Alex Sarah 現在又是Rebecca
There's more behind this than the codex.
我看這裡還有比法典更複雜的事
So you're an expert on romance now?
你現在倒變成個愛情專家了?
One who has loved not wisely,but too well.
一個在戀愛上不智而過於深情的人
- Othello. - Yeah. We all know how that turned out.
- 奧賽羅 - 對 咱們都知道劇情
You okay?
你還好嗎?
Pretty quiet on the way home.
回家的這一路上也太沉默了
Well,I didn't wanna break the spell.
我不想成為解除魔咒的人
Oh,look,honey.
親愛的 是這樣
Jill challenged me.
Jill挑戰了我
You ow that I didn't enter Quantico all that sure of myself.
你知道我加入匡提科時不很自信
But she tried so hard to beat me
但她卻非常努力地想超越我
that I worked my butt off to beat her.
我也使盡力氣試圖打敗她
- And... - Look at you now.
- 然後... - 看看你現在
No,that's not what I meant.
不 我不是想說這個
It's...it's just that I never thought
只是... 我從來沒想過
that I could finish as high as I did.
能夠走到這個位子
You know that.
這你是知道的
You're the reason I'm the man I am today.
因為你 我才成為現在這樣的男人
Continue.
繼續
I couldn't have gotten through this past year without you.
沒有你 我是撐不過這一年的
Or...any year.
或者說... 每年都是這樣
You know,it's still our anniversary.
咱們的紀念日還沒過去呢
I was hoping you'd say that.
我一直等著你說這句呢
Thank you,detective.
謝謝你 警探
Right,well,let's hope it does.
好 不錯 我們就希望事如所願吧
Bye. We'll take it from here.
再見 我們接管這事了
That was NYPD.
是紐約警局
Two days ago someone in Brooklyn commandeered a vehicle posing as an FBI agent.
兩天前在布魯克林有人自稱是FBI 徵用 開走了一輛車子
- Yesterday he struck again. - Did he flash a badge?
- 他昨天又這麼幹了 - 他亮出徽章了嗎?
NYPD doesn't know if it's real or not.
紐約警局還不知道它的真假
Or if it could be Siegel's.
也許是Siegel的徽章
Chances are slight that it is,but we need to check it out.
機會很渺茫 不過我們還是得查查看
Could be our first solid lead in two weeks.
可能是咱們兩周來的首次實質性進展
I want you and Jones on this.Two people I trust.
我要你和Jones來做這個 你們是我信任的兩個人
Well,1 1/2.
好吧 一又二分之一個人
Who is that?
那是誰?
Uh,no one important.
不是什麼大人物
Come up with something to catch this guy.Now go.
想點辦法 抓住這人 行動吧
- You seem nervous. - Just leave,just leave.
- 你好像很緊張 - 走吧 走吧
- Hey. - Neal Caffrey.
- 嘿 - Neal Caffrey
Do we know each other?
我們認識嗎?
Jill stone. I stayed up all night reading the case files of you two.
我是Jill Stone 我熬了一夜來讀你倆的案件卷宗
Couldn't put it down.
難以釋手
The good ones keep you up at night.
好東西總讓你熬夜
Mm-hmm. The bad ones even longer.
不好的熬得更久
He was just leaving.
他馬上就離開了
- I wasn't expecting you. - We're a secretive bunch.
- 我沒想到你來 - 我們是秘密組織
Tell me we're looking at the same thing.
快告訴我 咱們看到的是同一件事吧
Peter Burke uncomfortable.
Peter Burke覺得不舒服了
That's not his natural state.
這不是他的常態
You know she's FBI?
你知道她是FBI?
Well,it's not your run of the mill suit.
她穿的可不是你那質量平凡的制服
Not that she ever wears one.
倒不是她沒穿過這種東西
Look at the way she holds herself.Open.
看她的行為方式 開放自然
Totally exposed.
完全坦誠
Confidence and plenty of it.
有著充足的自信
Ooh. Oh,that's not the first time she's touched him like that.
哦哦 看來不是她第一次這樣碰他了
They have a past.
他們有段往事
Look at her eyes. All over his face.
看她的眼神 仔仔細細地打量著他的臉
Yeah,she wants to see if he still feels anything.
是啊 她想知道他還有沒有感覺
- Whoa what? - They slept together.
- 什麼? - 他倆上過床
- Peter? - Not recently.
- Peter? - 不是最近的事
All right,you know I heard he had a pretty serious relationship
我聽說他有過一次非常認真的戀情
with a female agent down at Quantico.
是在匡提科和一個女探員
She joined SSG.
她去了特別監控組
The CIA of the FBI?
FBI裡的中央情報局?
Those are some badass agents.
都是些不好惹的探員
That explains the confidence.
她自信滿滿的原因就在這了
That's Peter's ex.It has to be.
那是Peter的前女友 肯定是
I couldn't talk about the case in front of your wife.
我不能在你妻子面前談論這案子
White Collar related?
白領罪案相關?
I'm tracking a tech genius named Mason Sadowski.
我在追蹤一個技術天才 他叫Mason Sadowski
Doesn't look all that intimidating.
看起來沒那麼□人啊
In today's world that's what trouble looks like.
在現代世界 他這樣的才叫大麻煩
He's part of a team that invented a new and extremely dangerous microchip
他是為我們的一個頂級國防承包商發明
for one of our top defense contractors.
極度危險的新式微芯片的小組成員之一
- Then he decided he didn't wanna share? - Exactly.
- 後來他不想繼續分享成果了? - 沒錯
Must be a very important chip.
那芯片一定很重要
Something to do with decoding passwords.
和破解密碼有關
With it,a two-bit hacker could break through
有了它 任何一個二把刀黑客都能解譯
our most sophisticated security walls.
我們最精密的防火牆了
Low-hanging fruit for our enemies.
對敵人來說唾手可得啊
Yeah,he put it on the black market.
是的 他把芯片賣向了黑市
I've established a cover I.D. as a broker for Iran.
我建立了一個伊朗掮客的掩飾身份
Set the hook yet?
放魚餌了嗎?
- He swallowed it. - Good.
- 他上鉤了 - 好極了
Waiting for a buy time to reel him in.
我在等一個買入的時機 好把他抓住
My problem: Most buyers representing foreign interests come in twos.
我的問題是 大部分外資企業買家 都是兩人代表
In order for the ruse to work,I need a partner.
想讓計謀管用 我就得找個搭檔
Someone with undercover experience.
有臥底行動經驗的人
Someone you can trust.
信得過的人
More than any other agent in New York.
比紐約任何一個探員都信任的人
- Section Chief Bruce Hawes put the order through personally. - Oh,Bruce,huh?
- 部門主管Bruce Hawes私下傳達了命令 - 喔 Bruce是嗎
Not only Bruce.Your name gets dropped a lot in Washington.
不單是因為Bruce 你的名字常在華盛頓被提起
Nice to hear.
真不錯
You know New York,and I don't have GPS.
紐約市 你懂的 我還沒有GPS
Besides,you're the best. Next to me,of course.
此外 你還是最棒的 當然 排我後面
Oh,that was Quantico. This is now.
那是匡提科時 時過境遷啊
I'll set up the buy.
我會佈置好買入
This is gonna be fun.
這事一定會很有趣
- Got that too. - Here.
- 我也收到了 - 給
- Good to see you. - Take care.
- 見到你真好 - 保重
Bye.
再見
She left Peter with a lot to think about.
她離開後Peter可有的想了
Get back to work!
回去工作!
And still uncomfortable.
他還是很不舒服
- Oh,hey,you got plans later? - Why?
- 喂 你晚點有安排嗎? - 怎麼了?
ASAC gave us an assignment.
助理探員主管給了我們任務
NYPD informed Peter someone may be using Siegel's badge in Brooklyn.
紐約警局告訴了Peter 有人可能在布魯克林用了Siegel的徽章
All right,I'll coordinate with NYPD.
好 我會和警局方面協調
We'll need the perp's description and his M.O.
我們需要罪犯描述和犯罪模式
So we know what we're looking for.
這樣才知道要找什麼
Or we help him find us.
或者可以幫他找到我們
Jill's just an FBI agent who needs help on a case.
Jill只是在案子上需要幫助的FBI探員
That's it. End of story.
就這樣 沒別的了
You never look at Jones like that.
你可從沒那樣看過Jones
- Drop it. - Hold on a second.
- 忘了它 - 等一下
Does El know that your old ex is your new partner?
El知道你的老相好是你新工作搭檔嗎?
I'm gonna tell her tonight when it's more relaxed.
今晚氣氛輕鬆點的時候我會告訴她
All right,at least give up the details.
好吧 至少記得抹掉那些細節
- What broke you two lovers up? - I don't know.
- 你倆這對兒到底為什麼分手? - 我不知道
She went west,I went east.It doesn't matter anymore.
她去了西部 我來了東部 怎樣都無所謂了
- It always matters. - No,what matters
- 有所謂 - 不 有所謂的
is that you catch the guy flashing the badge.
是你得抓住亂揮徽章的那傢伙
All right,Jones and I are gonna cruise Brooklyn tonight in sheep's clothing,but...
好吧 Jones我倆今晚會 披著羊皮巡視布魯克林 但...
But what?
什麼?
The wolves need a sleeker wardrobe.
狼兒們想要漂亮點的羊皮
Yes.
是
Drop me off.
載我回去
Dinner's almost ready.
晚飯快好了
- Jill came to my office today. - I figured she would.
- Jill今天來了我辦公室 - 一猜就是
Why don't you pour me a glass of wine and tell me all about it?
你幹嘛不給我倒杯紅酒 好好講講?
What kind of wine is this?
這是什麼酒?
Oh,that's the bottle Mozzie gave us last Christmas you were afraid to open.
去年聖誕節Mozzie送的 你不敢開的那瓶
Still am.
還是不敢
- You expecting someone? - No.
- 你等人? - 沒啊
Oh...hi,Elizabeth.
哦 嗨 Elizabeth
Um,wow,it smells like Italy in here.
這裡聞著好意大利的感覺
I forgot people still make dinner.
我都不記得還有人做晚餐的
I forgot people just drop by.
我都不記得有人就順道來了
I'm so sorry I keep interrupting you.
真抱歉 不斷打擾你們
I should have called first,but we're just kind of in a rush.
我應該先打個電話的 但是我們真的很急呢
- "We"? - Oh,Peter.I found where the guy's holed up,
- 我們? - Peter 我發現那人躲哪了
so we gotta do recon on the thing now,right now.
所以我們要去做偵察 就現在
You guys workin' on a case together?
你們在一起破案子?
That's why Jill is in New York and since it was White Collar related...
所以Jill才來紐約 而且這案子是白領罪案...
- What's it about? - Mm,it's classified.
- 什麼案子? - 保密
Oh,well,nothing we discuss ever leaves this house.
我們討論的不會傳出這屋子
I'm sorry,hon.We can't discuss this one.
對不起 親愛的 我們不能討論這個
- You okay? - Why wouldn't I be?
- 你還好吧? - 怎麼會不好?
I'll call you on my way home.
回來路上給你打電話
- I'll try to get him home in one piece. - Yeah.
- 我會盡量把他完整送回家 - 是啊
Do you live in this?
你住在這裡?
When I have to.
當必要的時候
All you're missing is a fridge and a hot plate.
你只差一個冰箱和爐子了
- Well,I'm thinking about putting in a fireplace and jacuzzi. - That'd be nice.
- 我還打算放個壁爐和按摩浴缸 - 那不錯
How come you're still in the field?
你怎麼還在出外勤?
I mean,you had big ambitions way back then.
你以前可是志向遠大的
I expected you to be assistant director by now.
我還以為你現在會是總監了
I'm on a Washington track.For the time being,I'm serving double duty.
我在去華盛頓的路上 眼下有雙重職責
ASAC and Neal's handler.
主管兼Neal的監管人
I'm pretty happy doing both.
我很樂意兩個都做
- Peter... - What?
- Peter... -什麼?
You don't have to put up a strong front for me.
你不用在我面前故作堅強的
You were the supervisor of an agent who got killed.
你是一名遇害探員的主管
I know you're hurting.
我知道你很受傷
- The entire bureau is. - Yeah.
- 整個調查局都是 - 是啊
It's been hard to shake it.
這種感覺揮之不去
I lost my partner eight years ago.
八年前我失去了我的搭檔
Still can't.
現在也無法釋懷
Cruisin' for the bad guy in a sweet ride,just like Crockett and Tubbs.
開豪車追壞人 就像Crockett和Tubbs
I am living the dream.
真像在做夢
Did you base your entire future on Miami Vice?
你的未來就建立在邁阿密風雲上?
Ah,Hill Street Blues,Cagney & Lacey...
希街藍調 美國警花...
- any show about law enforcement. - I had a different perspective.
- 任何關於執法的劇我都看 - 我立場不同
Let me guess,rooting for the bad guys?
我猜猜 你支持壞人?
Only when they were good,Cagney.
當他們做好事時 Cagney
We've been driving around for about three hours.Where is this guy?
我們都隨便開了三個小時 那人在哪?
We were chasing a couple that robbed a bank in Pomona.
我們在Pomona追捕一對搶銀行的人
They split up. I followed the guy.
他們分開了 我追男的
Earl was following the girl. She pretended to surrender.
Earl 去了追那女孩 她佯裝投降
She shot him.
她開槍殺了他
Is that why you work alone?
所以你一個人做事了?
It wasn't my fault,but it still feels like it was.
這不是我的錯 但我還是覺得有責任
Siegel used to come to my office
Siegel以前常來我辦公室
and just wanna hear about my old cases.
想聽我講講以前的案子
He couldn't get enough.
他百聽不厭
I brought him here from Chicago.
是我把他從芝加哥帶來的
David was my responsibility.
我對David有責任
- Can't protect everybody. - No.
- 你不能保護到每個人 - 是啊
And you can't take their place.
你也無法替代他們
Even though sometimes you wish you could.
儘管有時你希望你能
- Any closer to finding the killer? - Not yet.
- 有殺手的線索了嗎? - 還沒
Today we got a potential lead.
今天我們找到一條可能的線索
You'll find him.
你會找到他的
Justice is not always as swift as we want it to be.
正義有時候來得沒我們預期得快
Isn't that our guy?
這不就是我們要找的人嗎?
Yeah,he's out of his room. Now's our chance.
是的 他離開房間了 我們有機會了
- What? - I don't know.Bad feeling.
- 怎麼了? - 不知道 有點不祥的預感
I hope we don't get jacked before our perp shows up.
希望嫌疑人出現前我們沒先被襲擊
Hold on a second.
等一下
Whoa,what are you doing?You know Peter doesn't like folks touching his buttons.
你在幹嘛? 你知道Peter不喜歡別人亂碰的
Trying to get a better view.
我想找個好的視角
Looks like your hope is about to come true.
看來你要願望成真了
- On your left. - Yeah?
在你左邊
- I need your car.Official FBI business. - Yep.
- 我要徵用你的車 聯邦調查局公用 - 好
Get out now! Criminal's getting away.
快出來! 壞人要逃走了
- Be cool,man! - How are we gonna get our car back?
- 冷靜的 夥計! - 我們要怎麼把車拿回來?
Real FBI.
貨真價實的聯邦探員
Hands on the roof.
手放在車頂上
What do you got?
發現什麼了?
I would have had you if I wore flats.
要是我穿了平底鞋一定比你快
Well,I never knew you to make excuses before.
你以前可從不找借口的
Okay,you won that one.
好吧 這次你贏了
- Savor it,because it'll be your last. - Okay.
- 好好珍惜 這可是最後一次 - 好的
Thanks for letting us in. Honeymooners,right?
謝謝你讓我們進來 蜜月套房對吧?
- Always forgetting something. - Si,senor.
- 我們總是落下東西 - 好的 先生
Come on,let's find a place to stash the gun in case we get patted down before the buy.
快 找個地方把槍藏起來 以防交易前被搜身
You think he took the chip with him?
你覺得他把芯片隨身帶著了?
If I thought so,I would have taken him outside.
要是這樣 我在外面就能抓了他
Then maybe he left it here.
那可能他放在這裡了
Give me the gun.
把槍給我
You could have had any assignment you wanted when we left Quantico.
你從匡提科畢業時 想去哪都行
Why Los Angeles?
為什麼去洛杉磯?
- Hey,that looks familiar. - Yeah.
- 那看上去很眼熟 - 對
Same guys we passed on our way in.
我們進來時碰到的同一群人
They might be competitive shoppers for our chip.
他們可能也是競購芯片的人
Let's find out who they are.
我們查查他們是誰吧
Take a selfie like we're a couple on a date.
我們裝成是情侶拍張自拍吧
Come on,closer.We gotta sell it.
靠近點 這樣才像
Neal,you got him?
Neal 你抓到他了?
You left him bleeding on the sidewalk.A bullet in his chest.
你任由他在路邊流血 胸口中槍
- An FBI agent. - One of us.
- 他是FBI探員 - 我們的一員
I didn't kill the dude.
我沒殺那人
I pulled that badge and gun outta the trash.I swear.
槍和警徽是我在垃圾堆裡翻出來的 我發誓
You know,when a murderer swears,
你要知道 當殺人犯發誓時
I tend not to believe them.
我都不相信他們
It was a Friday.
那是週五
About a month ago. When people cash their g-checks.
大概一個月前 大家去兌現政府支票時
Oh,yeah?What time of day was it?
真的嗎? 那是什麼時候?
Later. Almost dark.
晚些時候 有點天黑
Where were you before that? Between 3:00 and 4:00 P.M.?
那你之前在哪? 下午三點到四點?
I-I don't remember.
我 我不記得了
"I don't remember". Well,you know what?
"我不記得了" 你猜怎麼著?
It doesn't matter because you've got the badge and you've got the gun.
沒關係 因為你有警徽和槍
And your prints are all over them.
上面到處都是你的指紋
You're going down for this.
你要為此坐牢
- Let's go.My skin is starting to crawl. - No,wait,wait.
- 我們走 我都要起雞皮了 - 不 等等
When your guy got hit,I was inside Dante's Liquor.
你們的人中槍時 我在但丁酒館
- For an hour? - Waited till it emptied out so I could rob it.
- 一整個小時? - 等它打烊我好去搶劫
The place was crowded and full of cash on check day.
那地方擠滿了人 兌換日又多現金
Look,check it out.The store's got cameras. They don't lie.
查查吧 店裡的攝像頭不會說謊
Get in there with him.
進去看著他
- Head down to the liquor store.I wanna see that footage. - Yeah.
- 去酒館 我要看錄像 - 好的
Look,you got him to talk.
瞧 你讓他開口了
Peter.
Peter
You did everything you could.
你已經盡力了
- Are you okay? - You're awake?
- 你還好嗎? - 你還沒睡?
I always wait up for you.
我一直等你回來才睡
Well,sometimes you fall asleep.
有時候你先睡著了
Not this time.
這次沒有
Tell me all about it.
跟我說說
It's classified.
這是機密
Oh,come on.
得了吧
It's not like Jill will ever find out.
Jill又不會發現
I can't.
我不能說
We always discuss your cases.
我們總會討論你的案件的
I know,but I--and I can't wait to tell you about it.But...
我知道 我也很想告訴你 但是...
not until it's done.
要等結案後
What's so special about this one?
這個案子有什麼特別?
I'm sorry,it's... - Classified.
- 很抱歉 它... - 是機密
You understand,right?
你理解的吧?
Of course I do.
當然
I'm an FBI wife.
我是探員的妻子
Facial recognition scan pegged them as Eric Healey and Robert Bly.
面部識別掃瞄確定 他們是Eric Healey和Robert Bly
They're both ex-black ops.
都是前秘密行動隊員
They've been freelancing for some of our lesser known defense contractors.
他們自由受雇於一些國防承包商
They're high-end mercenaries.
他們是高級僱傭軍
Yeah,it does look like we're not the only ones hunting our genius.
看來不止我們在追捕這個天才
Rival defense contractors would do anything for that technology.
競爭對手會不惜一切代價取得這技術
I think these guys are looking to be the new sellers.
我覺得這些人想成為新賣家
Which means they're not gonna buy it.
這意味著他們不會買它
They're gonna steal it.
而是要偷它
Hey,Elizabeth Burke.
嘿 Elizabeth Burke
Bearing gifts in a brown paper bag.I can only imagine.
用棕色牛皮紙包著禮物 我只能想像一下了
Oh,it's just his lunch.
這只是他的午餐
He forgot it this morning.
他今早忘帶了
Why aren't you in there?
你為什麼不進去?
Uh,scratched off the need to know list.
呃 被排除在知情名單之外了
Yeah,me too.
好吧 我也一樣
Come on,let's go in.
走吧 一起進去
No,Neal,I'm not that kind of wife.
不 Neal 我不是那種類型的妻子
Well,I'm definitely that kind of C.I.
這樣啊 我倒是那種類型的犯罪顧問呢
No,I'll just leave it on his desk.
不了 把這個放在他的桌子上就行
All right.
好吧
What do we think of this Jill?
關於Jill大家有什麼想法?
There's need for further study.
還需要再觀察看看
I think she's lonely.
我覺得她很孤獨
Well,she lives out of an '86 Chevy.I doubt she throws a lot of dinner parties.
這個麼 她開一輛86雪佛蘭 我猜她不會經常辦晚餐派對
She never got married.
她沒結過婚
Peter could be the last man she ever loved.
Peter可能是她唯一愛過的男人
20 years is a long time to go without loving someone else.
二十年裡沒有其他男人 這可有點懸
You fall in love with Peter,you--you are in love.
和Peter戀愛以後 就這樣一直相愛到現在
I can't imagine those feelings ever going away.
我從沒想過這份感情會變淡
- Not completely. - Really?
- 不會完全淡去 - 真的假的?
Peter Burke?The man in the conference room?
Peter Burke? 那個坐在會議室裡的男人?
You have no idea.
你不明白的
This is good.
很好
We'll have Jones coordinate with NYPD.
我們會讓Jones去跟紐約警局協調
We'll get a current location of the SUV.
這樣我們就能獲得那輛SUV目前的位置
- He can trail it and give us updates of its whereabouts. - No.
- 他可以跟蹤那輛車 隨時告訴我們位置 - 不行
Peter.I think I was pretty clear.
Peter 我認為我已經說得夠清楚了
No one else can know anything.No one else can be involved.
沒外人知道 也沒外人插手
It's my case,my rules.
我的案子我說了算
It's our case.
是我們的案子
I brought you in on this.Don't make me take you off.
是我讓你參加的 別逼我把你撤掉
You brought it to White Collar,and I'm ASAC here.
你把這個案子帶到了白領犯罪小組 而我是這裡的助理探員主管
We'll do it our way or you're out.
要麼按我說的做 要麼你就走人
You're not serious.
你不是認真的吧
This face doesn't look serious to you?
我看起來像是在開玩笑嗎?
Okay...ASAC.
好吧... 助理探員主管
Jones keeps tabs,he reports back to us,but we don't tell him why.
Jones進行監視 向我們匯報 但是我們不能告訴他原因
Agreed.
同意
Yeah.
行了
- I'm gonna say hi to El. - Yep.
- 我要去跟EL打聲招呼 - 好
- Did you call her? - I did.
- 你給她打電話了嗎? - 打了
El couldn't have been sweeter.
El的態度好得不能再好了
- That's good,right? - It's terrible.
- 那不是很好嗎? - 那才恐怖
When she's upset with me,she makes herself irresistible and unavailable.
當她對我有意見的時候 她就會讓自己變得迷人卻又無法靠近
- Oh,nice technique. - Drives me crazy.
- 哦 高招 - 我要被逼瘋了
- All right,go home,talk to her in person. - I can't.
- 沒事的 回家吧 跟她當面談談 - 不行
Jill's setting something up.
Jill正在策劃一些事情
If I have to leave El mid-apology to meet Jill...
如果我還沒跟El道完歉 就又去見Jill的話...
So just assign a different agent to work with Jill.
那就另派一個探員去跟Jill合作
This case is too important.
這案子太重要了
- Besides,she doesn't trust anyone else. - Okay.
- 另外她不相信其他人 - 好吧
Is it about the case or is it about Jill?
這到底是因為案子 還是因為Jill?
I can talk to Jill about losing David.
我不能跟Jill談失去David的事
She's been through it herself.
她一個人承受了太多
And you don't wanna worry El any more than she already is.
而你也不願意讓El再擔心 因為她已經擔心得夠多了
I don't.She's been through enough this year.
我是不願意 這一年已經夠她受的了
Enough to believe that other bad things are possible.
夠受到會相信還有其他糟糕的事情 可能會發生
El knows that I'm in love with her.
El知道我愛她
- She trusts me. - Trust?
- 她相信我 - 相信?
Now you see it,now you don't.
說有就有 說無就無
I have to go.
我得走了
Thing I can't talk about?
那件不能談的事?
It's going down.
現在越來越糟了
- You must follow him. - Look,I am not following him.
- 你必須跟蹤他 - 聽著 我是不會去跟蹤他的
I'm not following my husband.
我不要跟蹤自己的丈夫
He's never given me reason not to trust him.
他沒有做讓我懷疑的事情
- Until now. - Mozzie.
- 直到現在 - Mozzie
You can trust truffles harvested in the Perigord region,
你可以相信松露是出產於佩裡戈爾的
bed linens handwoven in Madeira,and,for the most part,a Teddy bear named Mozart.
床上用品是在馬德拉手工縫製的 以及 大多數情況下 一隻名叫莫扎特的泰迪熊
But people?Almost never.
但是人? 基本是不可信的
You trust Neal.
你相信Neal
Neal is the reason "never" was preceded by "almost.
Neal是我用"基本"這個詞 而非"全部"這個詞的原因
"""I'm not following Peter."
我不要去跟蹤Peter
- You must. - I won't.
- 你必須去 - 我不去
- No.
- 必須去 - 不
Then follow the woman.
那就跟蹤那個女人
Or does your intrepid faith in the Suit extend to her as well?
難道你對條子堅貞不屈的信任 對她也適用?
- What do you have? - Yeah,Peter.
- 有什麼消息? - 是的 Peter
I followed the SUV to the village.
我跟著那輛SUV到了東村
They just parked and went into a restaurant.
他們停了車 進了一家餐館
- Thanks,Jones.Let me know when they leave. - Okay.
- Jones謝謝 他們走的時候告訴我一聲 - 好
Mercenaries just went into a restaurant.
僱傭兵剛進了一家餐廳
That meal should keep 'em on the shelf until we make the buy.
這頓飯應該能夠拖住他們 這段時間夠我們交易的
Well,they're after the chip.Why stop for a meal?
可他們在找芯片 為什麼突然停下吃飯呢?
They don't know our buy's going down now.
他們又不知道我們的交易停了
Even bad guys gotta eat.
壞蛋也得吃飯啊
You and the missus okay?She left the office in kind of a hurry.
你和你家那位還好嗎? 剛才她急匆匆地離開了
Yeah,she was just dropping by a sandwich.
沒事 她就是過來送個三明治
Sweet.I depend on the kindness of delivery guys.
真貼心 我吃飯就只能看外賣小哥的人品了
You never got married?
你一直都沒結婚?
Who would put up with me?
誰會受得了我啊?
- Yeah? - Yeah,Peter.
- 怎麼了? - 喂 Peter
I've got a bad feeling about this.
我有一種不好的感覺
We don't have eyes on the rear.
後門沒人盯著
Requesting permission for a walk-through.
請求批准進入
Can't he just do a simple walk-through?
能讓他光進去查看一下嗎?
It's not part of the agreement.You tell him to stand by.
規定裡沒這項 你讓他原地待命
Don't go.
不許去
She doesn't want me to go.You do.
她不想讓我去 可你讓我去
- Right. - Gotcha.
- 是的 - 明白了
- I'm going in. - Got it.
- 我要進去了 - 明白
- Mozzie was supposed to help me,but... - Bunion removal.
- Mozzie是要來幫我的 但他... - 拇外翻動手術了
- I heard all about it. - Okay.
- 我都聽說了 - 好吧
This is where I think she's staying.
我覺得她就住在這
I want you to come with me.
我要你跟我一起去
I hear she stays at the '86 Caprice.
我聽說她睡在86年的雪弗蘭裡
I saw a picture of them in front of this hotel.
他倆有張照片 就是在這家酒店門前拍的
Close.Extremely close.
關係親密 非常親密
And she looked smitten,but he looked like he wanted to go home.
她看起來一臉陶醉 但他臉上寫著想要回家
Because he's in love with you.
因為他愛你啊
I know that.What I don't know is her intentions with him.
這我知道 只是不清楚她對他打什麼主意
I mean,he's not an ordinary man,but he is a man.
我意思是 雖然他不是一般男人 可他也還是個男人
If they are there,it's for the case and that could be dangerous.
如果他們在這家酒店 那也是為了案子 可能會有危險
That's why I need you.
所以我需要你啊
If you don't go with me,I'm gonna go alone.
如果你不和我一起去 我就自己走
Wait.
等等
I'll drive.You're too angry.
我來開車 你正在氣頭上
I'm tired of sitting.Let's go.
總坐著好累 走吧
We're early.
現在還早
We'll catch him off guard.
我們要抓他個措手不及
Or tip him off.
否則就驚了對方
I've done this before,Peter.
我有經驗 Peter
Look,they're probably not even here.
你看 他們有可能根本就不在這
Okay,they're here.
好吧 他們在
That is not what it looked like.
這跟照片上可不一樣
It better not be.
最好別一樣
You know...
知道嗎...
I really thought I was gonna see both of them
我剛才真的以為 會看到他們兩個
sitting on stools so close to each other they were touching.
坐在高腳凳上 挨得緊緊的 摸來摸去
You know,Peter having a beer and Jill having whatever
Peter喝著啤酒 Jill隨便喝點什麼
women have when they're sitting with someone else's husband.
女人坐在別人老公身邊時 會點的東西
All right,don't jump to conclusions.
好啦 別急著下結論
Too late.Already jumped.
太晚了 已經下結論了
Wait at the bar.
你在吧檯那邊等
I'll pull a room number out of the desk clerk.
我去前台查房號
If...there is a room number.
如果... 如果他們真的開房的話
Mercenaries are gone.
僱傭兵跑了
They must have I.D.'d us and snuck out the back of the restaurant.
他們肯定認出我們了 然後酒店後門遛了
I want you to put the tac team on alert.I'm calling Peter.
你去讓特警準備 我給Peter打電話
SSG procedure.Radio silence.
現在是特別監督小組行動 無線電靜音
Okay,start tracking Peter's cell phone now.
好 開始定位Peter的手機
He might be walking into an ambush.
他有可能正進入對方埋伏
- Elizabeth. - Neal.
- Elizabeth - Neal
A man from Peter's file is in the bar.
Peter案子裡的一個人也在這酒吧
That's why they're here.It was the case.
這才是他們來這的原因 為了案子
I told you not to jump.
告訴你了別急著下結論
I'm sure Peter's looking for him.
Peter肯定在找他
I think I could stall him.
我想我可以拖住他
Call Peter for me,okay?
幫我給Peter打個電話 好嗎?
Elizabeth,don't do anything--
Elizabeth 什麼也別做...
Um,are you staying at the hotel?
嗯 你住這家酒店嗎?
Yeah,uh,I'm staying.You?
是 嗯 我住這 你呢?
No.Just getting a drink.
沒 只是來喝一杯
Are you in a rush?
你著急走嗎?
- What? - Well,sit with me.
- 什麼? - 那和我坐會兒吧
Have a drink.
喝一杯
- maybe later? - Why not now?
- 晚點好嗎? - 現在不行嗎?
I have a meeting.
我要去見個人
Um,how about you give me your phone
不如你把電話給我
- and I'll give you my number and you call me in a 1/2 hour? - Okay.
- 我把手機號留下 你過半小時找我 - 好的
- Ma'am,your check. - Oh,thank you.
- 女士 你的 - 謝謝
Thanks.
謝謝
- All right. - Thanks.
- 好的 - 謝謝
- Promise to call? - Promise.
- 一定打給我哦 - 一定
Neal,that's him.
Neal 就是他
Did you get a hold of Peter?
你聯繫上Peter了沒?
No.Voicemail.
沒有 轉留言信箱了
Wait here.I need to see where they're going.
你在這兒等著 我看看他們上哪兒去
Oh,no,I'm coming.
不 我跟你一起
All right,tell me everything that happened.
你剛才做了些什麼
Well,um,okay,I flirted with him.
好吧 我這個麼... 我勾搭了他
- He tried to flirt back,but he was not very good at it. - Keep going.
- 他想反勾搭回來 但挺不在行的 - 繼續說
He seemed anxious to leave.
他好像急著要離開
He said maybe meet up in 30 minutes and he put his number in my phone.
他說半小時後再聯繫 還把手機號存我手機了
He put his number in your phone?Let me see it.
他把手機號給你了? 給我看看
What is that?
這是什麼?
Some kind of new microchip.
一種微芯片
All Peter told me was that it's about security.
Peter只和我說過和安保有關
I think we found what he and Jill are looking for.
看來我們找到他和Jill要找的東西了
Shouldn't he be waiting for us?
他不是該在等我們嗎?
Like you said,we're early.
我們不是來早了嗎
He's playing it cool.
他淡定著呢
Honey,I told you,it's the wrong room.
寶貝我就說嘛 走錯房間
Hey,I saw you the other day.
我前兩天見過你
Taking pictures...of us.
在偷拍我們
We're honeymooners.
我們是來度蜜月的
We thought this was our room,but our key doesn't work,so I guess it isn't.
以為這間房是我們的 但鑰匙插不進 看來是搞錯了
There's only one room on this end.
這頭只有這一間房
We don't--we don't want any trouble.
我們可不想惹麻煩
We'll just be leaving,all right?
走就是了嘛
What's in the bag?
包裡是什麼?
Nothing.
沒什麼啊
Clothes.
衣服
Open it.
打開
Open it,or you go from honeymooner to widow.
快打開 不然就等著蜜月變寡婦吧
Buyers or feds.
你們是買家還是調查局的?
Cash says that you're either one or the other.
現金說明你們一定是其中之一
Third option.We're newlyweds who don't believe in credit cards.
還有第三個可能 我們是不太相信信用卡的新婚夫婦
He's an old-fashioned kind of guy.
他這人就是這麼老套
That I am.
我就這樣
I-I don't know who he is,but she's a buyer.
我不認識這男的 但她是買家
The deal was supposed to go down today.Right now.
今天本來準備要交易的 就約的現在
The chip!
芯片呢!
I hid it on a woman downstairs.
我在樓下藏在一個女人身上了
What woman?
哪個女人?
Wait.We're both buyers.
等等 我們都是買家
Iranian interests.
是代表伊朗方的
Well,at least I was until this morning.
至少今早還是
North Korea came calling.
朝鮮方又聯繫了我
- Our partnership wasn't gonna make it past the parking garage. - Son of a bitch.
- 我們倆根本就不是一路的 - 尼瑪
Their country would be very grateful if the two of you joined our team.
如果您兩位能加入我們的話 朝鮮將不慎感激的
Extremely grateful.
極其感激哦
Look,kill the both of them.
把他們倆都給我幹掉
You can take the money.
錢也歸你們了
I'll cut you in on my half of the chip.Just untie me.
芯片我算你們一半 解開我就好
All right,you have to go downstairs.
你得到樓下去
I have the chip.I'm going in.
芯片在我手裡 我要進去
Give it to me.I'll take it in.
那給我 我進去
Are you gonna help me get in there,or am I gonna have to knock?
你是幫我進去呢 還是要我自己來敲門?
Let's discuss this.
我們商量商量好了
I don't know who you're working for or what they're paying you,
我不知道你們為誰工作 或是收了什麼報酬
but the North Koreans will beat it.
但朝鮮肯定牛過他們
They can't even feed their own people.
他們連自己的國民都餵不飽呢
Shut up.
閉嘴
What are you looking for,newlywed?
你到底要想幹什麼 新郎官?
All right.
好吧
- You never saw this. - What is that?
- 你就當沒見過這個 - 這是什麼?
It's something Mozzie and I made.
我和Mozzie搗鼓的一樣玩意兒
Now go in there like you own the place.
現在你走進去 就當做是進自家門一樣
Show them the chip,but keep it away from them.
把芯片給他們瞧瞧 但放遠點
Okay,try to buy me 30 seconds.
幫我爭取30秒的時間
Careful.
小心了
I asked you a question,newlywed.
我問了你問題啊 新郎官
I've got what you want.
你要的東西在我手上
Hon,get out of here now.
寶貝 快出去
Th--that's her.
就是她
That's the woman I stashed the chip on.
我就把芯片藏她那了
He's right.
是的
It's,uh--it's in here.
就在這兒
It's,um--I have it.
在我手上
It's--it's in the phone case.
在手機殼裡
FBI.
FBI
Oh,that was incredible.
太牛叉啦
But don't do anything like that again.
但以後再也不許這樣了
I don't know if I can promise that.
這我可不能保證啊
All right,we got two men down.
逮捕兩人
Another typical day at White Collar.
這就是白領科普通的一天
Well,I fulfilled one of my fondest dreams.
實現了我夢寐以求的一個夢想
- Yeah,what's that? - Working with you.
- 是什麼呢? - 和你共事
It was fun.
很有意思
We did talk about that at Quantico a lot.
我們在匡提科的時候是經常這麼說來著
It lived up to expectations.
心想事成啦
But you had bigger dreams back then.
但你那時候的夢想要更遠大些
Washington.
去華盛頓
Soon?
很快了?
Once I've tied up all the loose ends here.
只要我收好所有尾巴就好
Yeah.I can't just bring anyone in to be Neal's handler.
我不能隨便找個人來當Neal的監管人
I gotta make sure they're up to the task.
我要確保來人能夠勝任
- Peter. - What?
- Peter - 怎麼了?
- There'll always be loose ends. - Yeah.
尾巴是永遠收拾不完的
Yeah,and there's one you might be able to help me with.
嗯 你也許能幫得上我一個忙
Uh,this one is a cold case that has been gnawing at me for 20 years.
這個疑案已經困擾了我20年了
Why California?
為什麼選擇去加利福尼亞?
You were top in our class.
你在班裡是數一數二的
You could have had any assignment you wanted.
你想去哪兒都成的
I took an assignment.
我接受了分配
First female SSG agent on the west coast.
西海岸第一個特別監控組女探員
- How could I turn that down? - I wouldn't have stopped you.
- 這叫我怎麼拒絕呢? - 我沒想阻止過你
You wanted New York.D.C.
你是想去紐約啊華盛頓的
That was your dream.
這是你的夢想
You ran.
你先跑了
You didn't chase after me.
你沒有追過來
You would have just run faster.
那你會跑得更快
You're right.I would have.
說得對 我是會的
At least this way we can remember Quantico as the beautiful thing it was.
至少這樣 我們就能把匡提科 當做最美的回憶了
Let's do that.
就這樣吧
Where you headed?
你接下來準備去哪?
Off to Miami.Another case.
去邁阿密 有另一個案子
Well,I hope another case brings you to New York again.
希望有案子能讓你重返紐約
Yeah,maybe I'll bring my El with me.
嗯 也許我就能帶我的El一起來了
- Male edition. - Good luck finding one.
- 男版的 - 祝你早日找到如意郎君
She's one in a million.
她可是萬里挑一的
Don't be afraid to talk to her,Peter.
別對她遮遮掩掩的 Peter
About anything.
什麼都是可以說的
I should have talked to you about this a long time ago,but I can't stop thinking about him.
我應該早對你說了 但我沒法不去想他
I can't shake the feeling that if I hadn't become ASAC he'd still be alive.
總是止不住去想 要是我沒當探員主管 他就不會喪命
Just trust me,okay?
相信我 好嗎?
- Can I open my eyes? - No,you can't.
- 能睜眼睛了嗎? - 不行
Step down--curb.Curb.
下來 有路牙子
There you go.
好了
It's not that big of a curb.
沒那麼高啦
I don't like surprises.
我不喜歡驚喜
- They never turn out good. - All right,we're almost there.
- 從來都不是什麼好事 - 好了 就到了
You know,you should know that walking the streets of New York blind
閉著眼睛走在紐約的大街上
is a recurring nightmare of mine.
可是我反反覆覆做的一個噩夢
You can open your eyes.
可以睜眼了
It's the window from the codex.
這是抄本裡的那扇窗戶
How did you ever find it?
你是怎麼找到的?
Agent Gruetzner used some of his underworld contacts.
Gruetzner探員動用了一些地下關係
It's beautiful.
美輪美奐啊
Not professional.
真不專業
No.
是啊
Not professional at all.
一點兒都不專業
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=http://ytet.org=-   proudly presents
-=伊甸園美劇 http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=伊甸園字幕站 http://ytet.org=- 榮譽出品 本字幕僅供學習交流，嚴禁用於商業途徑
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-Sync: YTET- 爱吃鱼的老虎  静静的生活
-=YTET-伊甸園字幕組=- 翻譯: 郭郭 安 Zzinc Muslin 泉雋戈弘 校對: 時差雪 時間軸: 愛吃魚的老虎  靜靜的生活
White CollarS05E07
妙警賊探 第五季 第七集